<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Novel Speed Writing</string>

    <!-- Credits -->
    <string name="app_title">Novel Speed Writing \n Application</string>

    <!-- About Page Text -->
    <string name="about_title">About Page</string>
    <string name="about_page">An Application Made By: Tommy Mertell \nThis application is an extension of a course that
        I teach on Udemy. While I am attempting to make my way into the developing world, I have been a professional
        Ghostwriter for over a decade. I have no college education and I have proven time and again that college is
        something I simply don\'t need. In order to survive in the Ghostwriting world you not only need to be able to
        write, but you need to be able to write fast with no chance of being hung up on such things as writer\'s block.
        As such, I have developed a method that allows me to turn a sentence into a book, article, and even screenplay
        by following very simple, logical steps. This application is not to ensure quality nor does it ensure that it
        will make you more creative. The only thing this application does is show how I take one sentence and turn it
        into a book. It is up to you to determine whether you will use this or not, how you will use it if you do, and
        to what effect this application will have on your writing experience.
    </string>

    <!-- Small Move Page Text -->
    <string name="start_small_move_big_title">Start Small Move Big</string>
    <string name="start_small_move_big">This is the most important part for any author who just started out on their
        own. Don\'t go big and don\'t waste your time trying to go big. You don\'t write a 90,000 word book out of
        nowhere and you shouldn\'t try. I did and it took me 7 years to complete my first novel. Then I wrote a second
        novel of the same time and it only took me 6 months. The difference was that I had the experience from the first
        novel. You build up from your first book. Sure, it is an achievement to get your first one in but you don\'t win
        a race by trying to run the biggest marathon for your first run. My suggestion is that you start small, you may
        even like writing small because you get more novelettes out. Small is in between 3,000 and 10,000 words. Once
        you\'ve made a couple at this size, you should then move on to bigger books at a slow pace so that you can
        perfect your writing before you write large scale books.
    </string>

    <!-- The Idea Page Text -->
    <string name="the_idea">The Idea</string>
    <string name="the_idea_intro">This is perhaps the easiest part because you just have to think of anything. However,
        some of us still have trouble with this when they first start out because of several factors. So, let\'s
        construct an IDEA.
    </string>
    <string name="the_idea_bold_text">An idea for a book is made up of 4 parts.</string>
    <string name="the_idea_protagonist">Protagonist</string>
    <string name="the_idea_protagonist_text">This is your hero or the person you will be following throughout your book.
        You can think one up or go to a random
        generator for names and work from there.
    </string>
    <string name="the_idea_antagonist">Antagonist</string>
    <string name="the_idea_antagonist_text">The antagonist is whoever or whatever the protagonist has to go against.
        They try to do the opposite of whatever the
        protagonist stands for.
    </string>
    <string name="the_idea_settting">Setting</string>
    <string name="the_idea_settting_text">The setting is where it takes place. If you want it in a separate world, you
        are gonna have to explain this to the
        reader. If you have it in this world, you need to tell them where and what area it will encompass.
    </string>
    <string name="the_idea_conflict">Conflict</string>
    <string name="the_idea_conflict_text">This is the core of your story and will determine the interactions between all
        of your characters. This is really
        simple and all it means is what the antagonist does that the protagonist must be against. \n\nI will be using
        this one for every segment afterwards.
    </string>
    <string name="the_idea_final_text">The Knight [Protagonist] must fight the Demon[Antagonist] to save[Conflict] the
        world[Setting].
    </string>

    <!-- The Description Page Text -->
    <string name="description_page">Description Page</string>
    <string name="description_page_intro">In this section, we will build off the previous section The Idea. In order to
        make a description, you need an idea to start with and this is where the logical progression takes its first
        steps. You have six different questions that will aid you in creating content.
    </string>
    <string name="description_page_questions">Who? What? Where? Why? How? When?</string>
    <string name="description_page_text">That may sound a little unrealistic, at first, but this method is how I turned
        an idea into a story. There are a few key points to be made here about when to use these questions. You are
        exploring your own book instead of creating your own book. This is similar to how an artist will see a vision on
        their canvas before they ever put paint brush to paint. You are asking these questions to learn about your own
        story while also writing your story in the same process.
        The what determines the subject of what will take place inside of that question. The where will determine the
        setting of the past, present, and future. The why will determine how that subject takes place. The how will also
        determine how that subject takes place. The when will determine the plot of the past, present, and future. The
        less common who will determine characters and their names. Now that those key points have been laid out, we can
        use them on the previous idea.
        The Knight must fight the Demon to save the world. \n\n

        • Who is the knight? \n
        • What is the knight like? \n
        • Where does the knight live? \n
        • Why is he or she a knight? \n
        • How did he or she become a knight? \n
        • When did the Knight start their struggle? \n
        • Why must it be the knight who fights? \n
        • What is the knight\'s fighting style? \n
        • Where will the fight take place? \n
        • Why must they fight? \n
        • How will they fight? \n
        • Who is the demon? \n
        • Why is he or she a demon? \n
        • Why will fighting the demon save the world?

        \n\nAs you can see, there are a lot of questions that can be asked for this one sentence and all of this
        revolves
        around being a highly skeptical person. In order to create your description, all you have to do is answer the
        questions that you ask. You do not have to answer them all right now, but if you can then it\'s better for you.
        These questions are a guide for you to follow.
    </string>
    <string name="description_page_result">
        Todd is a knight, a warrior of great skill and prowess, that lives in the kingdom of Kael. Todd became a knight
        after he accidentally rescued the prince with an unknown power that resided in him. The prince decided to make
        him a knight as a reward and Todd has since fought alongside the prince as a bodyguard. With his unknown power,
        Todd is the first and only magical knight in the land of Kael. Seeing the kingdom of Kael as a weak kingdom rich
        with untapped spoils the demon, Yiel, sees his opportunity to make his slave empire. As the only one who can
        wield both sword and magic, it is up to Todd to fight Yiel.
    </string>

    <!-- Page Summary Page Text -->
    <string name="page_summary">Page Summary</string>
    <string name="page_summmary_intro">The page summary is given different names depending on the industry that it is
        used in but it is basically a bigger description of the description. The point of a Page Summary is to use it to
        break your book up into the different sections you want to write about. We\'ll get into breaking it down into
        chapters in the next section, but, first, let\'s use our questions to make a Page Summary.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_questions">Who? What? Where? Why? When? How?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_setup">Todd is a knight, a warrior of great skill and prowess, that lives in the kingdom
        of Kael. Todd became a knight
        after he accidentally rescued the prince with an unknown power that resided in him. The prince decided to make
        him a knight as a reward and Todd has since fought alongside the prince as a bodyguard. With his unknown power,
        Todd is the first and only magical knight in the land of Kael. Seeing the kingdom of Kael as a weak kingdom rich
        with untapped spoils the demon, Yiel, sees his opportunity to make his slave empire. As the only one who can
        wield both sword and magic, it is up to Todd to fight Yiel.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q1">Who is the kingdom of Kael?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q1_answer">The kingdom of Kael is a small kingdom that has always had nice relationships
        with its people and its neighbors.
        Since Kael always helped out its neighbors and never tried to start any wars, the neighboring kingdoms left it
        alone. As a peaceful nation, the kingdom focused on intelligence and skill rather than brute force. This was
        something the other nations lacked and relied on Kael to supply.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q2">What is the kingdom of Kael like for Todd?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q2_answer">Todd was a servant for a good portion of his life, but he was well educated
        due to the fact that he lived in the
        kingdom of Kael.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q3">Where is the Kingdom of Kael?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q3_answer">As a harbor, the kingdom of Kael sat along the coastline surrounded by
        neighboring kingdoms that shared a
        continuous alliance with the kingdom of Kael.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q4">Why does Todd live in the Kingdom of Kael?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q4_answer">Todd was born into a servant family that had long lived as the royal servants
        of the household.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q5">Who is the prince?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q5_answer">Prince Lux was the youngest son in a line of five princes. While he is the
        last of the sons, he is often doted
        on as he is less brutish than his older brothers. As he passed his exams with flying colors, he was in line to
        be the next king as the kingdom of Kael had always decided their king based on academic aptitude rather than
        pure bloodlines.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q6">Where was the prince rescued?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q6_answer">The prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested on a
        smaller scale before, but one of his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q7">Why was it Todd that rescued the prince?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q7_answer">Todd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling to his
        death. Todd panicked at the sight and,
        without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change the direction of his fall so that the prince
        skidded over the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q8">What is Todd\'s relationship with the prince?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q8_answer">Before that, the prince and Todd had never crossed paths since the servants
        were never allowed to be in the same
        areas as the royal family.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q9">Why is his relationship like that?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q9_answer">The separation allowed the royal family to function as a normal family without
        becoming corrupt by seeing their
        power over people. As a normal family should, they still prepared their own meals, clothing, and everything else
        a family normally did. The servants were there to take care of the castle.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q10">Why does the prince choose to make Todd a bodyguard?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q10_answer">The only reward that Todd could be given as a servant was a promotion to a
        better paying position. Lux chose a
        bodyguard due to the fact that Lux wanted to repay Todd in other ways, such as teaching him battle tactics, with
        the hopes that the two of them would benefit from each other.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q11">What does his unknown power do?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q11_answer">Todd\'s unknown power is that he can infinitely teleport wherever he wants to
        and in whatever position he wants
        to be teleported into.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q12">Why does his unknown power make Todd the only magical knight?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q12_answer">The power does not cause him to lose any energy, which is why mages could not
        become knights as the two
        professions used up too much energy by themselves for one person to be able to do both.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q13">Why does Yiel see the kingdom as weak?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q13_answer">Since the kingdom is primarily made up mages, there is no brute force that
        could challenge Yiel\'s army if he
        nullified their magic.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q14">What does Yiel consider untapped spoils?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q14_answer">The kingdom of Kael is primarily made up of weak men and women, which were
        perfect for unresisted slave labor.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q15">Why does Yiel want a slave empire?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q15_answer">Yiel\'s ultimate goal is to conquer the entire world so that he can live off
        their souls forever.
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_q16">Why is Todd the only one who can fight Yiel?</string>
    <string name="page_summary_q16_answer">Since Todd\'s magic cannot be nullified and it does not have a cost, Yiel
        cannot stop or catch Todd.
    </string>

    <string name="page_summary_q_end">Now that we have answered the questions, we can put our answers into the
        description appropriately to get our
    </string>
    <string name="page_summary_result_title">Page Summary.</string>
    <string name="page_summary_result">Todd is a knight, a warrior of great skill and prowess, that lives in the kingdom
        of Kael. The kingdom of Kael
        is a small kingdom that has always had nice relationships with its people and its neighbors. Since Kael always
        helped out its neighbors and never tried to start any wars, the neighboring kingdoms left it alone. As a
        peaceful nation, the kingdom focused on intelligence and skill rather than brute force. This was something the
        other nations lacked and relied on Kael to supply. Todd was a servant for a good portion of his life, but he was
        well educated due to the fact that he lived in the kingdom of Kael. As a harbor, the kingdom of Kael sat along
        the coastline surrounded by neighboring kingdoms that shared a continuous alliance with the kingdom of Kael.
        Todd was born into a servant family that had long lived as the royal servants of the household. Todd became a
        knight after he accidentally rescued the prince with an unknown power that resided in him. Prince Lux was the
        youngest son in a line of five princes. While he is the last of the sons, he is often doted on as he is less
        brutish than his older brothers. As he passed his exams with flying colors, he was in line to be the next king
        as the kingdom of Kael had always decided their king based on academic aptitude rather than pure bloodlines. The
        prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested on a smaller scale before, but one of his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground. Todd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling
        to his death. Todd panicked at the sight and, without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change
        the direction of his fall so that the prince skidded over the ground. Before that, the prince and Todd had never
        crossed paths since the servants were never allowed to be in the same areas as the royal family. The separation
        allowed the royal family to function as a normal family without becoming corrupt by seeing their power over
        people. As a normal family should, they still prepared their own meals, clothing, and everything else a family
        normally did. The servants were there to take care of the castle. The prince decided to make him a knight as a
        reward and Todd has since fought alongside the prince as a bodyguard. The only reward that Todd could be given
        as a servant was a promotion to a better paying position. Lux chose a bodyguard due to the fact that Lux wanted
        to repay Todd in other ways, such as teaching him battle tactics, with the hopes that the two of them would
        benefit from each other. With his unknown power, Todd is the first and only magical knight in the land of Kael.
        Todd\'s unknown power is that he can infinitely teleport wherever he wants to and in whatever position he wants
        to be teleported into. The power does not cause him to lose any energy, which is why mages could not become
        knights as the two professions used up too much energy by themselves for one person to be able to do both.
        Seeing the kingdom of Kael as a weak kingdom rich with untapped spoils the demon, Yiel, sees his opportunity to
        make his slave empire. Since the kingdom is primarily made up mages, there is no brute force that could
        challenge Yiel\'s army if he nullified their magic. The kingdom of Kael is primarily made up of weak men and
        women, which were perfect for unresisted slave labor. Yiel\'s ultimate goal is to conquer the entire world so
        that he can live off their souls forever. Since Todd\'s magic cannot be nullified and it does not have a cost,
        Yiel cannot stop or catch Todd. As the only one who can wield both sword and magic, it is up to Todd to fight
        Yiel.
    </string>

    <!-- Chapter Summaries Page Text -->
    <string name="chapter_summaries">Chapter Summaries</string>
    <string name="chapter_summaries_intro">Now that we have a Page Summary, we can then break this down into Chapters,
        which can also be called Chapter Summaries. These will be the descriptions of each Chapter in your book. Now,
        since I don\'t feel like creating as book within a book, we\'ll only work with one Chapter (Chapter 1). To
        recognize what can make a Chapter, you need to look for three things. A Start or Continuation, Substance, and an
        End or Continuation.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_start">Start</string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_start_text">A start usually begins a new type of subject, such as switching from talking
        in a tavern to being at home. The
        two are not directly connected and can be started separately.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_sub">Substance</string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_sub_text">Substance is a personal choice, but it is a measurement done by yourself to
        determine how much starting material
        you need in order to flesh out the chapter. This can be one to an endless amount of sentences given an endless
        page summary.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_end">End</string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_end_text">The end is either the end of the book, the end of a subject, or the end of a
        twist. The end of a subject means
        that the actions have completely been contained within the previous chapter. The end of a twist means taking the
        subject, ending it in that chapter using an unexpected situation, and then continuing it into the next chapter
        so that you can explain it there.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_continuation">A Continuation</string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_continuation_text">A continuation means you are going to carry one subject you are talking
        about over to the next Chapter.
        Preferably, don\'t do this when you think you\'ve run out of room in a Chapter as it will often come across as
        sloppy. Instead, you should leave off with a false end, such as the character goes to sleep or goes off to get
        something.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_result_title">Now that we know that, we can choose our first chapter.</string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_result">Todd is a knight, a warrior of great skill and prowess, that lives in the kingdom
        of Kael. The kingdom of Kael
        is a small kingdom that has always had nice relationships with its people and its neighbors. Since Kael always
        helped out its neighbors and never tried to start any wars, the neighboring kingdoms left it alone. As a
        peaceful nation, the kingdom focused on intelligence and skill rather than brute force. This was something the
        other nations lacked and relied on Kael to supply. Todd was a servant for a good portion of his life, but he was
        well educated due to the fact that he lived in the kingdom of Kael. As a harbor, the kingdom of Kael sat along
        the coastline surrounded by neighboring kingdoms that shared a continuous alliance with the kingdom of Kael.
        Todd was born into a servant family that had long lived as the royal servants of the household. Todd became a
        knight after he accidentally rescued the prince with an unknown power that resided in him. Prince Lux was the
        youngest son in a line of five princes. While he is the last of the sons, he is often doted on as he is less
        brutish than his older brothers. As he passed his exams with flying colors, he was in line to be the next king
        as the kingdom of Kael had always decided their king based on academic aptitude rather than pure bloodlines. The
        prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested on a smaller scale before, but one of his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground. Todd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling
        to his death. Todd panicked at the sight and, without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change
        the direction of his fall so that the prince skidded over the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_result_wait">Oh, wait a minute. That\'s a bit long for a description and that\'s because
        there\'s a lot of stuff that
        doesn\'t need to be there. If something is a fact and not a substance, we refer to them as Plot Constants as in
        they are parts of the Plot that have to deal with the story, but don\'t ever actually change. Now we can chop of
        the Plot Constants and extract what we need.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_result_wait_result">The prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested
        on a smaller scale before, but one of his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground. Todd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling
        to his death. Todd panicked at the sight and, without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change
        the direction of his fall so that the prince skidded over the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="chapter_sum_not_done">However, we\'re still not done here because while we do have a substance we
        could split this up into two
        chapters. To determine how many chapters you should have, we should talk about word count and then we\'ll come
        back to break this down.
    </string>

    <!-- Word Count Page Text -->
    <string name="word_count">Word Count</string>
    <string name="word_count_intro">There are a lot of high and mighty, snooty and tooty fruity authors who hear the
        phrase \"word count\" and flip out. I\'ve heard things like \"It lowers the quality\", \"You shouldn\'t limit yourself\", and my favorite nonsensical no-proof claim \"You can\'t quantify creativity\". This is a topic that
        easily angers me because there is a difference between an Author and a Ghostwriter. An Author is usually out for
        the artistic win and only sees money as a side benefit. A Ghostwriter usually doesn\'t care what they are
        writing so long as they get paid. It\'s the difference between an artistic painter and a billboard painter. One
        does it for fun while the other has a job to do. Having said that, let\'s dive into how Word Count will
        determine how many chapters you can have. If you choose to write a Novelette, you need a minimum of around 3,000
        words in order to say that you have a short story. Therefore, let\'s start The Breakdown
        \n\nWord Count: 3,000
        \n\nThen you break up each section into usable chapters.
    </string>
    <string name="word_count_usable_chaps">
        The prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested on a smaller scale before, but one of his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground.
        \n\nTodd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling to his death. Todd panicked at the sight
        and,
        without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change the direction of his fall so that the prince
        skidded over the ground.
        \n\nThe prince decided to make him a knight as a reward and Todd has since fought alongside the prince as a
        bodyguard. The only reward that Todd could be given as a servant was a promotion to a better paying position.
        Seeing the kingdom of Kael as a weak kingdom rich with untapped spoils the demon, Yiel, sees his opportunity to
        make his slave empire. Since the kingdom is primarily made up mages, there is no brute force that could
        challenge Yiel\'s army if he nullified their magic. The kingdom of Kael is primarily made up of weak men and
        women, which were perfect for unresisted slave labor.
        \n\nYiel\'s ultimate goal is to conquer the entire world so that he can live off their souls forever. Since
        Todd\'s
        magic cannot be nullified and it does not have a cost, Yiel cannot stop or catch Todd. As the only one who can
        wield both sword and magic, it is up to Todd to fight Yiel.
        \n\nAs we can see, out of that large Page Summary, there are a total of five usable chapters. Since this is a
        story
        of just 3,000 words, we can keep it at five chapters but if this were a 10,000 word book then we would need to
        make each section a continuation of the last or we risk having small chapters mixed in with behemoths.
        Therefore, for five chapters of 3,000 words that means the book must have at least 600 words per chapter. This
        is what a full breakdown would look like.
    </string>
    <string name="word_breakdown">
        \n\nThe Breakdown
        \n\nWord Count: 3,000 words
        \n\nSections: 5
        \n\nWord Count Per Chapter: 600 words
        \n\nThe prince was attempting to use a flying machine that he had tested on a smaller scale before, but one of
        his
        brothers had broken the angle of one of the wings. When the prince attempted to fly off the roof, he quickly
        found himself plummeting to the castle ground. 600
        \n\nTodd had been cleaning the stables when he saw the prince falling to his death. Todd panicked at the sight
        and,
        without realizing it, teleported underneath the prince to change the direction of his fall so that the prince
        skidded over the ground. 600
        \n\nThe prince decided to make him a knight as a reward and Todd has since fought alongside the prince as a
        bodyguard. The only reward that Todd could be given as a servant was a promotion to a better paying position.
        600
        \n\nSeeing the kingdom of Kael as a weak kingdom rich with untapped spoils the demon, Yiel, sees his opportunity
        to
        make his slave empire. Since the kingdom is primarily made up mages, there is no brute force that could
        challenge Yiel\'s army if he nullified their magic. The kingdom of Kael is primarily made up of weak men and
        women, which were perfect for unresisted slave labor. 600
        \n\nYiel\'s ultimate goal is to conquer the entire world so that he can live off their souls forever. Since
        Todd\'s
        magic cannot be nullified and it does not have a cost, Yiel cannot stop or catch Todd. As the only one who can
        wield both sword and magic, it is up to Todd to fight Yiel. 600
        \n\nOnce you have this, you can then begin breaking the chapters down into paragraphs using the same method of
        asking questions and picking it apart. Once you have broken it down into paragraphs, all you have to do is
        answer the questions with your creativity.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_idea">IdeaActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_description">DescriptionActivity</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3925342661426751/5582564271</string>
</resources>
